# Kevin Gerstner



☑ sirkevinicus@gmail.com

github.com/SirKevinicus

314-614-2301

# **Relevant Experience**

## **Graphic Design Intern @ ArchCity Defenders**

MAY - AUG 2019 \\ SAINT LOUIS, MO

- » Created a digital art collection of clients using Photoshop for print and web marketing.
- » Illustrated graphics that were featured on the companies' social media pages.
- » Researched social justice issues and communicated key issues to affected communities.

#### **Portfolio Website**

Web Developer \\ 2021 \\ www.kevingerstner.com

- » Designed and coded a portfolio website using HTML, CSS/SASS, Bootstrap 5, and JS
- » Used Responsive Design and Mobile-first approach

## Computer Graphics Teaching Assistant @ University of Tulsa

AUG - DEC 2020 \\ TULSA, OK

I was the Teaching Assistant (TA) for CS-4613 Computer Graphics, which focuses on using OpenGL and Java to create graphic projects. I helped students learn concepts and graded several projects.

## Research Assistant @ University of Tulsa

OCT 2018 - APR 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Researched and co-authored a paper on the topic of HCl and Gender with Prof. Sandeep Kuttal entitled: "Remote Pair-Programming in Online CS Education: Investigating through a Gender Lens". The paper was presented in the 2019 VL/HCC (Visual Languages & Human Centric Computing) conference.

#### Knock-Out! Global Smackdown Board Game

Board Game Designer, Artist, Marketing \\ 2015 - 2019

- » Created over 150 unique card illustrations, box art, and graphics for marketing
- » Developed and maintained a Wordpress website for marketing
- » Designed, built, and launched a Kickstarter campaign

# **Summary**

Imaginative and self-motivated developer and designer with experience creating websites using HTML, SASS, JS, and jQuery. Graduated in 2021 with a B.S. in Computer Science and Art & Math minors. Experience leading projects in agile development & picks up new skills quickly. Excels at motivating self and others in a team.

## Skills

## **Programming Languages**

HTML • CSS • SASS • jQuery • JavaScript • PHP • C# • Java • C++

### **Tools & Platforms**

Git • WordPress • Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign • Netlify • Unity • Visual Studio

## Concepts

Responsive Design • Mobile-first • Website Optimization • User-centric design

## **Education**

## The University of Tulsa

2017 - 2021 \\ TULSA, OK

3.8 GPA. B.S. in Computer Science and B.S. in Computer Simulation and Gaming with Math and Art minors.

## **Interests**

Board Games, Overwatch, Art, Animated movies, Horror Games, Music, Coffee Tasting